# OGUNSEMOYIN ADEYINKA .D

I am a full-stack developer with experience in both front-end and back-end web development. I have a strong understanding of various web development technologies and can use them to create functional and user-friendly websites. I am also experienced in database design and development and understand how to develop efficient and scalable web applications.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**Decagon**, Benin — Full Stack Software Engineer

August 2022 - PRESENT

Part of a full stack web development team creating a progressive web version of a successful new book-a-ride application, Dispatch rider application (Swift-Rider).

### **SEE AUTO**, Benin — IT Specialist

January 2020 - December 2021

My team and I were responsible for the development of an online service website and implementation of new IT systems, as well as maintaining, upgrading, and troubleshooting computer hardware and software systems in the office.

### **EDUCATION**

### Adekunle Ajasin University, Akungba Bsc. Ed

DECEMBER 2013- DECEMBER 2017

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN EDUCATION

### **PROJECTS**

# Book a Ride App

An app that offers several features to make it easier for users to book a ride. Users can easily search for nearby drivers, select the type of vehicle they need, and even get an estimated price for the ride. The app also makes it easy to pay for the ride with a credit card or other payment method.

Link: <a href="https://github.com/YINCOOS/Ride-App">https://github.com/YINCOOS/Ride-App</a>

### 11 Babs Sarumi, Egbeda Alimosho Lagos Nigeria

**Phone:** +23470-3224-8112

Email:ogunsemoyinade@gmail.com

Github:

https://github.com/YINCOOS

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/adeyinka-david-ogunsemoyin-7a32051ba/

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Javascript
- Typescript
- React
- React Hooks
- Nodejs
- Express Framework
- GraphQL
- MongoDB
- Postgresql
- HTML 5
- CSS 3

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

**Scrumstudy:** Scrum Fundamentals Certified.

**Google Africa Developer Training**Program: Software Development.

# Google Digital Skills for Africa:

The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing.

**EFSET English Certificate** 

### **Dataville Research LLC**

Internship in International Development

### Swift-Rider App

Dispatch Rider App also provides businesses with the ability to customize their courier services. This includes the ability to choose the type of vehicle, delivery times, special delivery instructions, and more. This helps businesses to ensure their shipments are delivered on time and in the most efficient manner possible.

Link: Project Still in progress

### **StarWars Application**

A single page application (SPA) that displays all characters of the Star Wars Movie. Built with vanilla JavaScript, JQuery, HTML5, and CSS3.

**Technologies Used –** HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and JQuery.

**Category - Personal Project (Frontend)** 

Link: https://yincoos-starwars.netlify.app/